Lands which I've yet to see...
Races who I’ve yet to meet...
A tomorrow which I’ve yet to experience...
No matter what happens,
I...
will change the world!
Here lies the land where Sinbad conquered the Dungeon.
By doing so, he began his quest to find mysterious warriors across the world.
Thus as many predicted, Dungeons began appearing throughout the lands.
In short, the Era of Dungeon Conquerors has begun.
Magi: Sinbad no Bouken ・ Part 1
And so, Sinbad the Conqueror is now…
drifting.
Big Bro!
This is your final chance! This time, for sure!
From below?!
Damn it!
It's going to catch up.
This way!
If I don’t take him down here,
I won’t reach adulthood.
I’ll kill him… with the one shot I have!
No more…
Staying like this…
I don’t want that!
Over here, you monster!
Baal!
Lend me your power!
Fall, Thunder!
S-So cold…
Iceberg up ahead!
What a major setback!
With the number of icebergs emerging, we should reduce our speed.
No.
Continue full speed ahead.
You summoned me?
Dragul.
His Majesty is enraged by the matter concerning the Dungeon.
Also, Serendine-sama has been shamed thanks to Sinbad.
Normally, you would have been stripped of your military position.
However, Safu General Barbarossa-sama has ensured that His Majesty give you at least the rank of a watchdog.
Big Brother has…
Partevia’s pride, the assassins of Sham Lash.
Take these men with you and deliver Sinbad’s vessel to His Majesty.
Furthermore, about Sinbad’s whereabouts...
He heads northward.
You are forbidden to fail again. Now go!
I will stake my very life on it.
If we move forward like this,
we’ll arrive at Imuchakk.
A remote region, home to a savage race of ill repute.
Is he there?
Woah, it really is huge!
It’s called a Rampaging Unicorn.
They usually live in the Southern seas
but occasionally travel all the way up here.
That’s amazing.
And to think that you were trying to defeat it with one shot!
Big Bro…
You finally did it?
You really did it!
I knew you were better at more than just swimming!
That's my Big Bro!
Alright!
Damn, I wanted to see it.
But why is it burnt?
And who are you?
Me?
I’m Sinbad.
A woman’s beauty sure travels around the world, doesn't it?
What’s your name?
I’m Pipirika.
Nice to meet you, Pipirika.
And um…
Come to think of it, I haven’t asked your name, have I?
Hina.
He’s called Hina.
Big Bro is already 21 years old,
but he still only has his given name.
But now that you've defeated the Rampaging Unicorn,
you’ll finally get a warrior’s name!
With this, that person will acknowledge you too.
That person?
Strong, sweet… all women including myself admire her.
After all, she’s Imuchakk’s number one beauty.
Wow!
What kind of a place is Imuchakk?
What kind? Let’s see…
It’s completely white.
I don’t mean it like that…
More like…
What kind of leader does it have and such?
Our father is the chief.
Really?!
Great! Take me there too.
Sinbad…
Our people don’t allow outsiders among us.
I don’t think a lot of good will come of your visit.
I don’t mind.
Unknown lands...
Unfamiliar people…
I want to see the entire world…
in order to change it!
I…
It’s beautiful, isn’t it?
You've been gazing at this scene the entire time?
Yes.
I’m sorry.
The Rampaging Unicorn.
I stole your thunder.
But you…
You saved your little sister in an instant, didn’t you?
That was cool.
Was it?
Pure white lands...
A race that dwells in the Poles...
Strange homes…
And beautiful ladies too!
Imuchakk is a country of snow and ice.
Welcome back to you both,
my children.
Father!
We have returned.
And who are you?
I’m Sinbad.
I’m on an adventure to see the world—
This is Imuchakk.
This is no place for outsiders!
Father…
Sinbad is our—
My son, now you’ve finally become a warrior.
From this moment forward,
this clan—this village—needs your protection from enemies.
Remember that.
Yes…
Tonight will be the Maharagan!
Come, it is time to prepare for the festival!
Now then…
Sinbad has entered the village of Imuchakk.
This has become rather troublesome.
The people of Sham Lash have already begun to take action.
Doing as they please!
They are people of darkness.
You can’t tame them.
Also...
What’s a Maharagan?
It’s a traditional Imuchakk festival.
It used to be a coming-of-age ceremony to receive a warrior’s name and rank
and also a ritual to thank the Goddess of the Sea.
Now that you’ve defeated the Rampaging Unicorn, Big Bro,
along with having your name,
you’ll become a real warrior!
In truth, during the time you two were gone,
strange things appeared.
Strange things?
A building which I have never seen before has appeared farther up north.
It’s the perfect place to choose new warriors.
Hina, you shall also go and conquer—
You can’t!
You can’t get close to that.
What?
That’s a Dungeon.
In my country Partevia,
a building like that appeared as well and many people died.
I’ve heard of it too.
All the soldiers who entered were annihilated
and it was eventually conquered by a single young man.
That was me.
What are you trying to say?
I won’t forgive anyone who makes a fool of us.
Is that what they call a Conqueror's Sign?
Yes, that's right.
The Djinn of that Dungeon resides in it.
It is customary in Imachakk to ensure that the strong receive the finest hospitality.
Please forgive my rude behavior up until now.
It’s only natural to be wary of strangers.
All the more when you’re the chief who looks out for his entire clan.
That’s why I’d like to make a request.
Don’t allow anyone close to that Dungeon.
I understand.
You have my word.
Oh. Big Bro, have you already spoken with that person?
No, I’m…
You’re a warrior now.
You should quickly tell that person too.
Stop it!
Right now, a person like me…
Big Bro, what’s wrong?
It’s started!
Hurry!
Come! Now is the time for the Maharagan,
the celebration of a man becoming a warrior and time to show our thanks to the Goddess of the Sea.
Now that you’ve defeated the Rampaging Unicorn, Big Bro,
along with having your name,
you’ll become a real warrior!
You’re wrong.
I heard he ran away from the Rampaging Unicorn again.
I’m sorry. I can’t go out with a man who isn’t a warrior.
What, did you fail again?
You will become a warrior. You’re the Chief’s son, aren’t you?
You can definitely defeat it, Big Brother!
My son.
Hurry and become a warrior.
I…
Big Bro.
You always come here when you have something on your mind, don't you?
This sure brings back memories.
Wow, that’s so good!
Pipirika, you wanna give it a go?
I’m fine.
You’ll get better once you practice.
I can teach you.
Okay!
But you know, I want to watch you do it, Big Bro!
Sure.
Now that you’re a warrior,
you must have a lot on your mind.
But you know,
even though you're a warrior, you'll always be the same kindhearted Big Bro, right?
Let’s go.
Tonight is your festival.
Right.
Come on!
If we don’t hurry, Father will get Sinbad drunk!
Huh? Where’s Sinbad?
His threshold for alcohol is low so he’s resting now.
You gave him too much to drink, didn’t you?
What are you saying?
If a man can’t hold his alcohol, then what will become of him?
What’s wrong?
Can you take it?
This is a special sort of brew, you know.
You’re so beautiful…
But hang on…
So tall…
That’s our target.
Ah, wait…
Piece of cake.
Die!
Wait!
A kid?
Naughty children need to be disciplined properly!
Is that all?
As I thought, I’m more than enough to finish the job.
What?
What are you smiling about?
Too bad.
Now then.
Who are you?
Are you a member of Partevia’s troops?
This brat!
To think they would involve even a kid like you.
Hey!
What’s with that attitude?
And at your age on top of that.
I don’t know who your superiors are
but your parents will be sad, won’t they?
Shut up.
What did you say?
That’s some attitude towards people older than you.
Sinbad, he’s an assassin. Be careful.
I know.
That’s why I’m asking him firsthand, right?
N-No, that’s not what I meant…
No. You gotta teach brats like him everything from the basics.
You got that?
You think you can talk like that just because you’re an assassin?
Don’t you think your mom and dad will be disappointed?
That’s why I told you to shut up!
My parents are long gone!
I killed them when I was six after all!
What? You scared now?
Don’t you dare say such things so proudly.
I pity you.
What’s with you?
Those eyes…
You’re a kid yourself, you asshole!
Sinbad!
You little…!
Don’t come any closer!
As if you could understand...
Chief, are you unharmed?
Shut up!
I’ll definitely kill you!
Sinbad!
Just who were those guys…
Is that wound you got okay?
It’s nothing serious.
Come on, let's hurry and get ready for the festival.
More importantly, who were those guys?
Probably some people from the Partevian Army.
They’re after me.
Isn’t that something you shouldn’t take lightly?
Why?
Because I defied the country.
And some other stuff.
Aren’t you afraid?
You can’t return to your country and your life is being targeted.
This could last for the rest of your life, you know.
For me,
I only follow my own destiny. That's it.
Also,
I will overcome this wave.
Sin…
I…
Just a little bit more!
Big Bro, it’s time!
Could you go on ahead before me?
I’d like to calm down for a bit.
I see.
Come as soon as you can, okay?
We’ll see you later.
Come on, hurry up! We’ll be late!
Sinbad!
Big Bro has…
Big Bro…
In order to be a real warrior…
He said he’s going to the Dungeon!
Will I become a warrior?
If I obtain the power of the Dungeon,
I’ll be just like you.
Everyone except one who wants to be king will be slaughtered.
That’s how the Dungeon works.
To achieve their ambitions, many men tried
and died in the process.
Then, Big Bro…
Don’t worry.
I won’t let Hina die.
But!
Whether you come back alive or not…
We can't be certain of that, right?
I know this:
I will not die.
This is…
Don’t lose heart.
Even I…
If I obtain the power of the Dungeon,
then I’ll finally become a warrior.
I will have everyone acknowledge me.
This is…
Where am I?
A Dungeon?
Have your travels been led by the Dungeons, Sinbad?
What do your eyes see all the way up there?
Sinbad…
Is this your fate?
I’ll do it.
I won’t… let anyone interfere.